Good morning. I don't know who needs to hear this, but your religion, your political party,
your sports team, they are not gangs. Gangs aren't a good thing. Okay. Gangs extort and
exploit others who they feel are weaker than them. Gangs use violence. Gangs have rivals
that they consider to be their enemy because they are taking money or territory or most importantly,
the ability to exploit and extort away from them. The cops are a gang. The United States is a gang.
Islam is not a gang. So when y'all act like other parties and other religions and other sports teams
are your opponents that you need to fight and die for, you're bugging. Your religion is supposed to be
your connection to God. Your political party is that which you use to attain and achieve that which
you want to live by, via the government. Your sports team is entertainment, baby. The fact that they trade
should let you know it's not real rivalries. Hope this helps. I have a Tuesday.
D.C. and Bottom Wall, you're up next. I'm outside y'all doing what I can to decolonize minds on my
mission-driven book tour for my new book, What Would the Ancestors Say?
They say books won't change the world. Tell that to every colonizer that burned them.
Come on out, be in community, buy a book and get it signed. RSVP at AmandaSeals.com.
Come on out, be in community.